Contato

+351 918 433 867 (Mobile) nuno.condinho@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/nuno-condinho-1617b83 (LinkedIn)

Principais competências

Sales Management
Account Management
Negotiation

Languages

Spanish (Full Professional)
Portuguese (Native or Bilingual)
English (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Retail Sales Management
Sales Performance Measurement
and Reporting
Body Language for Leaders
Lean Services Management - Mini
MBA

Customer Experience: Journey Mapping

Honors-Awards

Country Manager of the year 2013 Best National Sales Representative 1997

Area Director of Year - Europe

Nuno Condinho

Director Vendas Operações | Director-Geral | Customer | Imobiliário | Digital / Cowork Flex Office Space / Turismo

Lisbon Area, Portugal

Resumo

Business Leader and specialist in Sales organizations, with over 15 years management experience, has integrated and managed teams in different countries and multi-cultural environments. Developed an extensive experience in starting-up, developing and running business in different Industries. Over the last 12 years, managed flexible workspace service teams, collaborative workspaces and communities, as well as co-work solutions, and Digital Real-Estate services. Leader in Sales, Operations and Customer Service management positions in the Accor Group and IWG / Regus and Spaces in different regions - leading branches in Eastern Europe (based out of Paris), Portugal & Spain, Middle East (Bahrein, Qatar, Saudi Arabia, Dubai) and Africa (Algeria, Senegal, Morocco, Mozambique, Zambia, Namibia, Botswana, Mauritius; based out of South Africa).

Upon returning to Portugal, led and restructured OptimHome Digital RE Agency and recently joined SALES FACTORY, a startup specialized in Sales Strategy and Business Advisory. Developed consulting projects in tourism, real estate, healthcare, construction, advertising, hotels, among others.

Experiência

Sales Factory General Manager maio de 2018 - Present (2 anos) Lisbon Area, Portugal

Partner at Sales Factory, a Sales & Management Advisory firm.

Sales Factory helps companies growing their business.

We create value by supporting companies in the analysis, planning and execution of commercial, organizational and customer relationship processes.

The team is also giving support to companies setting-up in Portugal, outsourcing sales teams and looking into opportunities in commercial realestate, building models to increase returns around cowork, workspaces and community space.

OptimHome Immobilier Country Manager março de 2017 - fevereiro de 2018 (1 ano) Lisbon Area, Portugal

PropTech / International Digital RE Agency

Managing company's operations, reporting into the CEO.

Managing a staff of 80+, and being responsible for the operation's full scope & profitability, focusing on the commercial and operational sides of the business. Have fully restructured the operation, by redefining the Business Plan, based on 3 axis: new digital tactical plan, sales development and people plan: recruiting 60% of new sales representatives

Regus

10 anos 5 meses

Country Manager - Southern Africa dezembro de 2013 - março de 2017 (3 anos 4 meses) Southern Africa

REGUS, IWG is the world leader in flexible workspace and co-working solutions, holding the brands: Regus; Spaces; HQ; Signature; No18.

I was invited to develop the business across southern africa, based out of Johannesburg, South Africa. Have led company's global operations at a regional level, reporting into the CEO, actively contributing to the Global strategy. Was running the business throughout several Southern Africa Countries: Botswana, Mauritius, Madagascar, Namibia, Mozambique and Zambia.

Managing a staff of 50+, and being responsible for the operation's full scope & P&L, focusing in driving the profitability of existing mature business, whilst building the team and look for further development opportunities, by identifying new buildings and locations.

Managing both Sales & Marketing and operations, ran daily activities on each of the 16 business units, across the different countries, always focusing in delivering the best customer experience, with the best team.

Started Regus operation in Mozambique up to 7 locations in 3 cities (through organic and acquisition plan), opened-up Namibia and Botswana, and grew the operation by over 60%+ in Mauritius & Zambia, through the opening of new business units, leading the process in full: Business Plan, people recruitment, sales & marketing & operations plans definition and implementation.

We have multiplied the business size by 5x over the period, started with 3 branches and left with a total of 15.

Country Sales and Operations Director - Iberia janeiro de 2010 - dezembro de 2013 (4 anos)
Portugal

Managing business for Portugal and Spain, running sales, marketing & operations, having a total staff of 80+ people.

Ran the entire operation, focusing in delivering an excellent customer service, by ensuring we had the best team, with the best product. Driving the P&L with particular focus on sales, revenue growth, and cost control. I was also responsible for developing the business, having expanded to 4 new cities across Iberian península: Porto, Bilbao, Málaga, Valência

We achieved a growth of 25%+ in budgeted profits over a 3 year period

Area Operations Director - Middle East and North Africa novembro de 2006 - dezembro de 2009 (3 anos 2 meses)
Paris, Dubai, Bahrein

I was initially tasked to give regional support for eastern Europe and Middle-East, assisting & coaching the local directors, based on a matrix structure, during 1 year.

Was later invited to lead the region directly, specifically for Western Gulf and North Africa.. Having a staff of 40+, we had 7 countries: Saudi Arabia, Bahrain, Qatar, as well as NAF countries - Algeria, Morocco, Tunisia, and later the opening of Senegal branch. Also supervised the Business Development, being actively involved in analyzing potential new locations & buildings, reviewing building standards and space solutions.

Our key to success was having the best team, with the best product. Driving the activity with a particular focus on revenue growth, and cost control.

Have achieved a growth of 15%, focusing in growing sales and streamlining operations efficiency, by consolidating mature business and opening new branches in Algeria, Senegal and Qatar.

Accor Services
Sales and Marketing Director
2002 - 2006 (4 anos)
Lisbon Area, Portugal

Sales & Marketing leadership, with a staff of 15 FTE, developed the sales & marketing departments in 2 business units: Incentive marketing and Employee Benefits. As part of senior management team was actively involved in the restructuring and growth of Accor Services in Portugal, turning the business around from negative to positive EBITDA

Media Capital Edições
Account Manager
2000 - 2002 (2 anos)
Leading 2 Magazines commercial activity, with a team of 5;
selling advertising space and events sponsorships

Formação acadêmica

Católica Lisbon School of Business and Economics
PAGE, Business Administration and Management, General · (2018 - 2018)

Instituto Português de Administração e Marketing - Lisboa Master's degree, Marketing Management · (1999 - 2004)

Universidade Aberta
Frequência de Licenciatura, Gestão · (1998)